[音乐]
[MUSIC]
&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：Brendan发明了脚本标签，因为他有这个问题，
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: Brendan invented the script tag because he had the problem,
你把放在页面上的脚本放在哪里？
where do you put the scripts that go on the page?
由于HTML是文本格式，
And since HTML was a text format,
他决定以文本形式将程序发送到浏览器。
he decided to deliver the programs to the browser in text form.
&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：这是不寻常的，因为大多数语言都会提供
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: Which is unusual because most languages will deliver
执行站点的可执行文件。
an executable to the execution site.
JavaScript将源代码交付到执行站点，并且
JavaScript delivers source to the execution site and
就是因为这个问题。
it was because of this problem.
所以当他们开始写作时，他们发现的第一件事
So one of the very first things they found when they started writing
利用JavaScript的页面是当您显示
pages to take advantage of JavaScript was that when you display
Navigator 1和Mosaic上的那些页面，脚本将显示为文本。
those pages on Navigator 1 and on Mosaic, the script would show up as text.
这是因为HTML规则，如果你看到一个标签而你不认识它，
And that was because of the HTML rule, if you see a tag and you don't recognize it,
继续走。
just keep going.
那是非常尴尬的。
And that was hugely embarrassing.
他们不可能回到过去
And there is no way they could go back in time and
告诉那些老的浏览器不要这么做，所以他们想出了这个可怕的黑客。
tell those older browsers not to do that, so they came up with this terrible hack.
他们将脚本包装在HTML注释中。
They wrapped the script in HTML comments.
只要你没有使用减号，那么脚本就会被隐藏
And as long as you're not using a minus minus, then the script will be hidden and
没人会看到的。
no one will see it.
我仍然看到人们这样做。
I still see people doing that.
所以如果你看到有人这么做
So if you see anybody doing that,
告诉他们从1996年开始就没有这个必要了，所以别说了。
tell them this hasn't been necessary since 1996, so knock it off.
&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：Microsoft添加了语言属性，因为他们打算
&gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: Microsoft added a language attribute because they intended
为了去掉JScript并用他们自己的VBScript替换它，
to kill off JScript and replace it with their own VBScript,
VBScript是Visual Basic的一种方言。
VBScript being a dialect of Visual Basic.
但那并没有发生，讽刺的是，
That didn't happen, and the irony is,
它没有发生的原因是因为他们在JScript上做得非常好。
the reason it didn't happen was because they did such a good job on JScript.
如果他们做了惯常的事情，那么JScript
If they'd done their usual thing, then JScript
不会达到临界质量，JavaScript可能会失败，而且
would not have gotten critical mass and JavaScript probably would have failed, and
他们本来有机会偷走市场，但他们没有。
they had a chance to steal the market, but they didn't.
因此，事实证明，JavaScript是唯一种可靠地运行于所有
So as it turned out, JavaScript was the only language that ran reliably on all
浏览器，所以这是每个人都使用的语言。
browsers, and so that was the language everybody used.
我见过的唯一使用VBScript的人是罪犯和广告商。
The only people I've seen using VBScript are criminals and advertisers.
&gt；&gt；扬声器2：[笑]&gt；&gt；Douglas Crockford：其他人
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: [LAUGH] &gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: Everybody else
正在使用JavaScript。
is using JavaScript.
他们添加了source属性，这是一个非常好的主意
They added the source attribute which was a really good idea
因为事实证明，你不应该把脚本标签放到页面上。
cuz it turns out, you should not put script tags onto pages.
如果将脚本放入单独的文件中，
If if you put scripts into separate files,
然后它们可以被缩小，它们可以被gzip压缩，它们可以被缓存。
then they can be minified, they can be gzipped, they can be cached.
所有这些对于页面启动性能都非常好，这一点至关重要。
All of which are extremely good for page startup performance, which is critical.
如果你把它们放在页面上，你就得不到任何这些好处。
If you put them on the page, you don't get any of those benefits.
所以所有的东西都应该放在单独的文件中。
So everything should be in separate files.
最后，W3C不喜欢language属性，因为它们不是自己编的。
Then finally W3C didn't like the language attribute because they didn't make it up.
所以他们用自己的东西替换了它，他们说这是必需的。
So they replaced it with their own thing and they say that it's required.
但事实证明，如果您使用的是source属性，并且您应该这样做，
But it turns out, if you're using a source attribute, and you should,
它是关于资产的MIME类型是什么的权威的服务器，
it is the server that is authoritative on what the MIME type of the asset is,
而不是请求它的标签。
not the tag that requested it.
因此浏览器需要忽略它。
So the browsers are required to ignore it.
W3C说它是必需的。
W3C says it's required.
我说不用了，没必要。
I say leave it out, it's not necessary.
只是浪费空间。
It's just a waste of space.
所以，document.write是我希望Brendan Eich有过的最糟糕的想法。
So, document.write is I hope the worst idea Brendan Eich ever has.
他认为与浏览器交互的工作方式是
The way he thought that interaction with the browser was going to work was
JavaScript将在页面递增加载时运行。
that JavaScript would run as the page is being loaded incrementally.
而JavaScript在运行时，
And that JavaScript, as it's running,
可以在解析文档时将新的HTML文本插入到文档中。
can insert new HTML text into the document as it's being parsed.
有点可怕。
Which was kind of awful.
所以我看不到它被用得很多了，除了
So I don't see it being used very much anymore except by
罪犯和广告商，好吗？
criminals and advertisers, okay?
&gt；&gt；扬声器2：[笑]&gt；&gt；道格拉斯·克罗克福德：我明白了
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: [LAUGH] &gt;&gt; Douglas Crockford: I see
广告商经常使用这个。
advertisers use this a lot.
在网络广告的早期，存在着大量的欺诈行为。
In the early days of web advertising, there was a huge amount of fraud.
所有的广告公司都在互相敲诈。
All the ad companies were ripping each other off.
误报图像视图和其他事情。
Misreporting image views and other things.
所以他们想出了这个协议
So they came up with this agreement that the way
一个广告放置可以工作是你把一些广告脚本放在你的页面上。
an ad placement can work is you put some ad script on your page.
它将对前往广告服务器的脚本标记进行document.write。
It will do a document.write of a script tag going to an ad server.
然后那个将返回代码，该代码将执行以下操作
And that one will then return code which will do
脚本标记转到另一台服务器的document.write。
a document.write of a script tag going to another server.
他们可以做一些这样的事情，去不同的地方
And they can do several of those things, going off to different places and
它允许所有这些不同的公司或机构分别计算这件事。
it allows all of these different companies or agencies to separately count the thing.
这样他们就能在实际发生的事情上达成一致。
So they can all agree on what actually happened.
但其后果之一是他们可能会增加巨大的延迟
But one of the consequences of that is they can add huge delays to
页面的呈现。
the rendering of the page.
因为所有的事情都要等到所有的广告重定向完成，而且
Because everything has to wait until all those ad redirections get finished, and
这也是一个巨大的安全漏洞。
it's also a huge security vulnerability.
因为这些服务器中的任何一个都可以发送他们想要的任何东西。
Because any of those servers can be sending anything they want.
如果他们发送了一些肮脏的东西，就会发生不好的事情
And if they send something nasty, bad things happen and
没有办法防御它。
there's no way to defend against it.
所以这一切都很糟糕。
So that's all pretty awful.
所以我不建议任何人再用它。
So I don't recommend anybody use it ever again.
所以不幸的是你把
So unfortunately where you put
页面上的脚本标记可能会对页面加载时间产生巨大影响。
a script tag on a page can have a huge impact on the page loading time.
放置脚本标签的正确位置应该是头部。
The correct place to put script tags should be in the head.
因为这是元，对吧？
Because it's meta, right?
脚本不是内容，它们是元。
Scripts are not content, they're meta.
所以这就是头的作用。
So that's what the head is for.
不幸的是，浏览器在脚本加载方面极其无能。
Unfortunately, browsers are extremely incompetent at script loading.
所以如果你把脚本放在脑袋里，
And so if you put scripts in the head,
然后所有解析阻塞，直到脚本加载、编译和执行。
then all parsing blocks until the scripts load, compile, and execute.
这意味着如果身体中有任何需要加载的图像，
Which means that if there are any images in the body that need to get loaded,
在所有脚本完成之前，它们甚至不会开始加载。
they don't even start to load until all the scripts are finished.
这可不好。
That's not good.
所以Steve Souders发现我们需要将所有脚本移动到底部
So Steve Souders figured out that we need to move all the scripts to the bottom of
取而代之的是尸体。
the body instead.
这对性能很好，但对可靠性很差，但是
Which is great for performance but terrible for reliability, but
这就是我们现在做的。
that's what we do now.
他还建议我们缩小并gzip脚本文件，
He also recommended that we minify and gzip the script files,
这是非常好的建议。
which is very good advice.
他还建议我们尽可能减少脚本文件的数量
He also recommended that we reduce the number of script files as much as possible
通过将它们连接在一起。
by concatenating them all together.
他们真的是很好的理由来推荐它，因为HTTP令人难以置信地
And they're really good reasons to recommend that because HTTP is incredibly
不能加载脚本文件。
incompetent at loading script files.
因此HTML请求中的串行延迟
And so the serial delays in HTML request
交易对你的伤害真的很大。
transactions really hurt you badly there.
因此Souders建议您可以将所有脚本文件一起计算，
So Souders recommended that you can count meet all of your script files together,
并将它们转换为一个大文件，这样您就可以避免一些HTTP开销。
and turn them into one big file and that way you avoid some of that HTTP overhead.
不幸的是，这会导致其他问题。
Unfortunately, that leads to other problems.
它完全中断缓存，因为每个页面都有不同的
It completely breaks caching because every page will have a different
它将要加载的组合脚本集。
combinatorial set of scripts it's gonna load.
所以有可能
So the likelihood that one
组合脚本文件将再次重用非常低。
combined script file is gonna be reused again is extremely low.
它还引入了错误，因为可能会发生某些错误，
It also introduces bugs because there are certain errors that can happen,
如果您将大量文件放在一起，则这些文件是无法更正的。
which are not correctable if you put lots of files together.
例如，您可能有一个文件是由一个不称职的白痴编写的，他
For example, you might have one file that's written by an incompetent idiot who
依赖于分号插入，并将其连接到其他人的文件上。
depends on semicolon insertion and that's concatenated onto someone else's file.
并且将插入分号的位置不再是
And the place where the semicolon would be inserted is no longer
由于串联而导致插入站点，现在文件失败。
an insertion site because of the concatenation and now the file fails.